In the last lesson we talked about the future how to talk about things we would like to do things that
上一课我们讲了未来如何谈我们想做的事情
will happen different levels of certainty and in this course we've been really focused on different
会发生不同程度的确定性，在本课程中，我们一直专注于不同的
situations and different topics different specific skills.
情况和不同的主题不同的具体技能。
But I want to in this lesson and the next lesson focus on some things you can do on a daily basis to
但我想在这一课和下一课中关注一些你每天可以做的事情
practice so that your mind can develop the habits that it needs to develop so that you can build the
练习，以便您的思想可以养成它需要养成的习惯，以便您可以建立
right habits to become a good English speaker.
成为一名优秀的英语演讲者的正确习惯。
I think this course wouldn't be complete unless you had the correct habits not only the knowledge that
我认为除非你有正确的习惯，否则这门课程是不完整的，而不仅仅是知识
you need but the correct habits to be able to speak clearly.
你需要的只是正确的习惯才能说得清楚。
So we're going to go over some exercises some things that you can do on a regular basis on a daily basis
因此，我们将进行一些练习，一些你可以每天定期做的事情
to practice all of the things that we're learning in this course.
练习我们在本课程中学习的所有内容。
Some things you can do to build the correct habits.
你可以做一些事情来建立正确的习惯。
Habits are so important when it comes to speaking a language.
说到说一门语言，习惯非常重要。
If you know everything but you don't have the right habits then the things that you know won't help
如果您什么都知道，但没有正确的习惯，那么您知道的事情将无济于事
you a lot when it comes to speaking saying what you want to say.
你经常说你想说的话。
So I want to make it very clear that you need to learn all that stuff.
所以我想非常清楚地表明你需要学习所有这些东西。
You need to know all that stuff but then you've got to have the right way of thinking and you've got
你需要知道所有这些东西，但你必须有正确的思维方式，你有
to have the right habits and the right way of thinking is the first step toward becoming a better speaker
拥有正确的习惯和正确的思维方式是成为更好的演讲者的第一步
and having those good speaking habits.
并拥有那些良好的说话习惯。
OK so doing a little bit of practice every day little exercises can help develop your your mind so that
好的，所以每天做一点练习 小练习可以帮助你发展你的思维
you feel comfortable when you want to say something when you want to use the things that we're learning
当你想说点什么时，当你想使用我们正在学习的东西时，你会感到很自在
in this course.
在本课程中。
So we're going to go over for some basic words a few things you need to know then we'll get into some
所以我们要复习一些基本的单词，一些你需要知道的事情，然后我们会进入一些
specific exercises that we can do.
我们可以做的具体练习。
We're going to talk about one called that I call stitching and I'll show you what that means in a second
我们将讨论一种我称之为缝合的方法，我会在一秒钟内告诉你这意味着什么
but basically stitching is linking things together creatively and then we're gonna go into something
但基本上拼接是创造性地将事物连接在一起，然后我们将进入一些东西
called simplification.
称为简化。
So we need to understand what we've seen what we've read so that we can simplify it in a way which is
因此，我们需要了解我们所见所闻，以便我们可以简化它
really natural and find out where the things that are unnatural or maybe redundant are.
真的很自然，找出不自然或多余的东西在哪里。
We'll go into that when we get into each exercise.
当我们进入每个练习时，我们将讨论它。
So let's get started.
所以让我们开始吧。